Guide to the Gerald Gillespie Papers SC0581
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2000-025
  - Restricted materials
    - Grades Sem II, Spring 1972 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Grades, Fall 1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Grades, Spring 1973 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Grades, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Minnesota Exams and Papers, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Strachota (Set 2), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Lieder, U. (Review), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Lieder (Set 2), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Salaries, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Provostial, Senate, and Decanal Searches, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Comparative studies graduate students, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Humanities program students, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Wittmann, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Grad students, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - GS Special Ablaze, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - GG "New" Applicants, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Adelson, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Search GS, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Bill Petig, 1994-1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Kathryn + Brigitte, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Wellbery (Set 3), 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Search Lists, 1976-1980 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - GS Junior Position, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - GS Search, thru 1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Finalists, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Restricted Item from David Wellbery, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Restricted Item from "Faeminae Clarissinae", Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2000-069
  - Abraham, Ruth Anne (Dec. 6, 1976-Feb. 1, 1979) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Allerdissen, Rolf (July 17, 1973-March 2, 1975) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Anderson, Ellen (Dec. 26-27, 1990) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Arnold, James (1993-Jan. 7, 1994) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bai Xiao-Dong (Dec. 26, 1985-Feb. 14, 1986) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Balakian/Nalbatian, Anna (Jan. 17, 1990-May 19, 1997) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bauschinger, Sigrid (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Beeler, Stanley W. (U. Alberta) (Sept. 1, 1988-May 23, 1989) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bentley, Eric (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Berlin, Jeffrey (Nov. 4, 1989-June 20, 1991) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Biddle, Michael (Nov. 30, 1982-April 26, 1985) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bjornson, Richard (Jan. 31, 1991-Feb. 18, 1991) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Black, Joel (Sept. 14, 1978-Nov. 19, 1990) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Blume, Bernhard (Jan. 8, 1974-Oct. 24, 1976) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Böhler, Michael (Nov. 30, 1970-June 7, 1993) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bové, Paul (Oct. 15, 1973-March 10, 1983) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Brady, Patrick/Judy (Sept. 20, 1992-Nov. 24, 1996) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Brady, Patrick (Feb. 1-3, 1990) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Braendlin, Hans (Nov. 10, 1972-March 8, 1987) (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bramel, Marie Claude (Oct. 26, 1972-July 31, 1974) (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Cardona, Rodolfo (Nov. 4, 1972-Nov. 10, 1974) (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Carpenter, Bill (March 23-April 25, 1988) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Chancellor, Gary L. (Sept. 17, 1985-Jan. 2, 1986) (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Clarke, Dana (Dec. 26, 1972-Jan. 1, 1976) (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Coleman, James (March 16, 1979) (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Corral, Wilfrido H. (Dec. 21, 1992-Jan. 18, 1993) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Cottrell, Alan P. (Sept. 7, 1973-Sept. 6, 1975) (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Crossen, Karen (March 19-Dec. 19, 1967) (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Davis, Robert (May 4, 1981-Jan. 29, 1984) (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Delaney, Neil (Nov. 5, 1971-Oct. 20, 1989) (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Demetz, Peter (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - DeMichiel, Linda (May 30, 1975-Dec. 1979) (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Davidson, Cathy (Nov. 15, 1973-May 14, 1974) (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Davis, Lisa (Oct. 12-Dec. 19, 1983) (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Dietze, Walter (July 3, 1980) (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Dutu, Alexandru (March 29, 1979-Oct. 5, 1990) (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Dyck, Joachim (Nov. 14, 1969-June 2, 1973) (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Dycus, Jamie S. (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Dimic, Milan V. (May 21, 1990-March 26, 1995) (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Esslin, Martin (April 10, 1984-Nov. 5, 1988) (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Early, Dennis (April 22, 1977-May 12, 1978) (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Eckhardt, Caroline (June-October 1997) (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Engebretsen, Rune (Dec. 6, 1984-Feb. 10, 1985) (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Exner, Richard (Feb. 14, 1974-Dec. 4, 1975) (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Fallon, Daniel (May 14, 1997-March 29, 1984) (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Flaherty, Gloria (July 14, 1980-Dec. 5, 1987) (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Fore, Toni (April 20-May 24, 1990) (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Firchow, Peter E. (Sept. 17, 1979-June 10, 1980) (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Fleischhauer (Sept. 27, 1974-July 12, 1979) (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Freedman, Joseph S. (Nov. 5, 1993) (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Fuegi, John (Dec. 22, 1973-March 20, 1980) (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Garber, Frederick (Oct. 15, 1973-May 26, 1987) (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Garber, Klaus (Sept. 29, 1983-Jan. 16, 1984) (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Garstin, Marguerite (Jan. 12-20, 1989) (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Geerts, Walter (Nov. 15, 1985-March 21, 1998) (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Gonzalez, Oscar (May 14, 1997) (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Grotzer, Peter (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Gottschalk, Mary (Feb. 17, 1978-Aug. 29, 1983) (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Goldman, Peter B. (Oct. 3, 1975-July 21, 1977) (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Gowen, Dale (Dec. 5, 1977-Oct. 7, 1983) (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Gustafson, Susan (March 6, 1983-Jan. 2, 1991) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Hawkins, Stephanie (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Hamburger, Kate (November 28, 1973-April 14, 1975) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Hannah, Richard (Nov. 23, 1983-Dec. 27, 1978) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Heller, Erich (Aug. 15, 1973-Sept. 30, 1975) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Hoffman, Ann (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Holthusen, Hans Egon (Sept. 2, 1973-June 8, 1975) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Hoell, Andreas (May 26-June 17, 1987) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Hanak, Miroslav J. (Nov. 20, 1987) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Hoffmeister, Gerhart (Sept. 18, 1972-Nov. 21, 1990) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Haga Toru (Jan. 19, 1996-Jan. 1, 1999) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Hoyt, Giles R. (April 24, 1965-Oct. 12, 1989) (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Hyams, Barbara (March 4, 1983-Jan. 15, 1989) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Ingram, Forrest L. (Feb. 5, 1972-Dec. 11, 1978) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Kant, Hermann (Oct. 24-Nov. 7, 1979) (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Keady, Sylvia (Jan. 13, 1976-Oct. 21, 1979) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Kerr, Cynthia (Aug. 26, 1975-June 16, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Killy, Walter (Aug. 22, 1973-July 15, 1975) (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Koc, Richard (feb. 16, 1980-Feb. 13, 1981) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Koopman, Helmut (Oct. 24, 1973-July 16, 1975) (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Kore, Clea (April 7, 1977-Sept. 29, 1983) (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Kowalik, Jill (Oct. 20, 1983-April 17, 1985) (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Kushner, Eva (Oct. 18, 1984-April 11, 1999) (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Leventhal, Robert (Feb. 26, 1976-Dec. 23, 1981) (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Levinsky, Ruth (Feb. 2-23, 1972) (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Lewis, Mark (Jan. 22, 1983-Jan. 14, 1991) (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Leifer, Amira (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Lieberman, Gerald J. (Dec. 12, 1980-Feb. 25, 1981) (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Liddle, Susan (May 20, 1986-Jan. 11, 1988) (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Liddle (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - LoCicero, Vincent (June 18, 1970-Sept. 22, 1972) (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Lange (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Leibowitz (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Low, Edward J. (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Lohner (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Matas (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - McCarthy, John (1994 Vanderbilt meeting) (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - McConeghy, Pat (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - McQueen (1980 and after) (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - McQueen (1979 and before) (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Mehl (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Meyer (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Mico, G. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Miller, I.K. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Moeller (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Mugge-Meiburg, Beth (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Morewedge, R. (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Martin, Nikki (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Neubauer (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Naumann (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Newman, Diane (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Neumann (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Neuswanger (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Norgaard, Rolf (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Prier, Ray (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Pagel, K. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Paolucci, Anne (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Peelaers, Carine (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Padgett (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Penrose (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Pike (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Pereira, Amalia (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Politzer (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Predmore (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Raabe, Paul (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Rather, L.J. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Rey (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Rindisbacher (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Ricardo-Campbell (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Remak, Henry (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Riechel, Donald (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Rolleston, James L. (Sept. 1968) (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Rose, Marilynn (Oct. 4, 1972-Aug. 26, 1976) (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Rosen, Robert S. (Dec. 15, 1969-Oct. 12, 1972) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Rumold, Rainer (Jan. 15, 1975-Sept. 16, 1981) (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Ruibal, Jose (Nov. 6, 1971) (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Shaffer, Elinor S. (Nov. 26, 1986-May 10, 1989) (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Shaffer, E.S. (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Smith, Charles (January 14, 1971-July 3, 1973) (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Sokel, Walter H. (March 6, 1974-March 22, 1976) (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Spalek, John M. (June 25, 1970-March 10, 1974) (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Spellerberg, Gerhard (Sept. 9, 1971-June 8, 1973) (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Skrine, Peter (March 21, 1983-April 2, 1990) (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Sperberg, Michael (June 2, 1975-September 10, 1981) (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Sengupta, Shil (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Seidlin, Oskar (Jan 18, 1974-Feb. 7, 1985) (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Schmidt, Gerard F. (May 3-Nov. 14, 1974) (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Sandor, Andras (Dec. 31, 1970-Nov. 20, 1974) (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Spariosu, Mihai (Aug. 19-Oct. 22, 1990) (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Sastre, Alfonso and Genoveva Forest (Nov. 14-Dec. 13, 1974) (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Schings, Hans-Jurgen (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Schantz, Ned (Dec. 11-22, 1992) (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Schone, Albrecht (Jan. 24, 1973-Aug. 20, 1975) (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Schulz-Behrend, George (Sept. 24, 1967-Dec. 20, 1971) (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Stackhouse, Janifer Gerl (June 1973-Nov. 19, 1976) (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Szarota, Elida Maria (Nov. 29, 1970-Nov. 23, 1971) (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Schwarz, Egon (June 27, 1977-Jan. 4, 1971) (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - von See, Klaus (Sept. 12-16, 1980) (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Spitz, Lewis (March 24-July 5, 1975) (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Tinsley, Royal Lilburn, Jr. (Sept. 22-Oct. 10, 1977) (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Tisch, J. Herman (June 12, 1970-Feb. 7, 1972) (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Tonelli, Giorgio (July 8, 1971-May 25, 1978) (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Tötösy, Steven (Nov. 17, 1994-Dec. 7, 1995) (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Weisenberger, Klaus (Sept. 24-Nov. 5, 1970) (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Wells, Lawrence (June 17, 1975-Nov. 16, 1976) (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Weiner, Marc (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Wellwarth, George E. (June 1, 1970-Sept. 22, 1973) (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - von Wiese, Benno (Nov. 28, 1973-Dec. 16, 1975) (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Witte (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Wolfe, Mark (June 22-Dec. 11, 1990) (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Werlen, Hans-Jakob (1984-1985) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Yip, Wai-Lim (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Weisstein, Ulrich (April 1, 1976-Dec. 9, 1995) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Weisgerber, Jean (Dec. 26, 1983-March 18, 1989) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Wellek, Rene (Dec. 17, 1973-Jan. 25, 1983) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Warnke, Frank J. (Feb. 19, 1972-Jan. 18, 1980) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Zhouhan, Yang (Dec. 1, 1989-Jan. 3, 1990) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Yob, David (Jan. 6-March 10, 1983) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Zapf, Wolfgang (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Zorach, Cecile Cazort (June 2, 1986-May 21, 1987) (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Zipser, Richard A. (Oct. 12, 1981-Dec. 8, 1990) (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Zilcosky, John (Dec. 1, 1991-May 28, 1998) (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Zilcosky
  - Zahareas, Anthony (Nov. 7, 1974-Aug. 5, 1982) (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, A (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, B (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, C (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, D (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, E (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, F (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, G (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, H (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, I (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, J (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, K (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, L (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, M (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, N (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, O (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, P (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, Q (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, R (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, S (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, T (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, U (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, V (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, W (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, X-Y (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, Z (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, unsorted (6 folders) (Box 4, Folder 39-44)
  - MLA newsletter (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - MLA -- classical studies and modern literature (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - MLA '89 Back File (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - MLA Rom. 1989( Wash D.C) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - MLA '89 Classics & Mod. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - MLA '89 ( General) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - MLA New Orleans '88 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Program C. MLA (1987) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Program Committee MLA 1985-86 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - MLA Program Committee (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - MLA SFO 1987 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 1986 MLA (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - MLA 1985 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - GG (MLA 84) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Soundup Special Session MLA 83 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - MLA New York 1983 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - MLA - Galdos Sem. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - MLA Coer. 18th- 19th Cen (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - MLA Los Angeles 1982 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - MLA New York 1981 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - MLA Houston '80 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - MLA Spanish 4 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - SFO MLA 1979 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - MLA 1976 of Seq. (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - MLA (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Delegate Assembly (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - MLA '91 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - MLA Toronto 1993 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - MLA Newsletter (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - MLA- Classical Studies and Modern Languages (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - MLA '89 Back File (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - MLA Rom. 1989( Wash D.C) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - MLA '89 Classics & Mod. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - MLA '89 ( General) (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - MLA New Orleans '88 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Program C. MLA (1987) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Program Committee MLA 1985-86 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - MLA Program Committee (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - MLA SFO 1987 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 1986 MLA (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - MLA 1985 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - GG (MLA 84) (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Soundup Special Session MLA 83 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - MLA New York 1983 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - MLA - Galdos Sem. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - MLA Coer. 18th- 19th Cen (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - MLA Los Angeles 1982 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - MLA New York 1981 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - MLA Houston '80 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - MLA Spanish 4 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - SFO MLA 1979 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - MLA 1976 of Seq. (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - MLA (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Delegate Assembly (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - MLA '91 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - MLA Toronto 1993 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Cruz, Arnaldo (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Jose Bower (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Africa, D. (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Wm Davis (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Conrad, Marty (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Campbell, Marsha (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Busch, J. (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2005-206
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2015-055
  - Comparative HIstory of Literatures in European Languages, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Benjamins/RPF/Contract, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - RPF (ating fraction of ed. correspondent), 1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - RPF Addresses: Contributions + Reviews, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Contacts w/ Colleagues, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - RPF Editorial Team, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - RPF Style Guidelines, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - RPF Style Sheets, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - RPF Harmonization, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - RPF General Bibliography, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Earlier CC Reports on CC Prose, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Interim Report May, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Albert, Claudia, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Aldridge, A. Owen, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Andermatt, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bernauer, Marlens, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Black, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Ceserani/Zanotti, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Chaves, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Dieterle, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Manfred Engel, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Figuiera, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Gerber, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Giacomoni, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Gorp, Hendrik van, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Grabovszki, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Graeber, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Guerrero-Straoham, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Halse, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Hoffmeister, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Isbell, John, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Klinkert + Willams, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Kummorling-Maibauer, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Lorant, Andre, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Maertz, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Martin, Elaine, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Nemoianu, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Paatz, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Rossbach, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Schmitz-Emams, Monika, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Smoot, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Spiridion, Monica, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Steigerwald, John, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Szegedy-Maszak, Mihaly, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Takayuki, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Talvet, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Kingston CC Sept. 27+28 travel arrangements, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Kingston Report Supplement, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Amsterdam CoCo, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Interim Report February, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Romantic Prose Narrative Recruitment, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - RNFP (Nemoaiana), 2003 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Rom. Subseries, undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Ablamowicz, Aleksander, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Alvarez, Emilio Jose, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Burwick, Frederick, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Curbet, Joan, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Braungart, Wolfgang, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Burwick, Frederick, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Buescu, Helena, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - D'Angelo, Biagio, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Dick, Alex, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Esterhammer, Angela, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Gottsche, Dirk, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Kagialis, Takis, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Korytowska, Marie, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Larson, Svend Erik, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Leiteritz, Christiane, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Miller, Scott, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Pagni, Andrea, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Perkins, Pam, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Peterson, Carla, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Rossner, Michael, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Santilli, Nikki, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Skwara, Marta Anna, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Sporl, Vive, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Stewart, Neil, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Svane, Marie Louise, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Wang, Ning, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - RPF Intro (mat. for revision), 2002 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Roman Discourse V.A., undated (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Chapters Offered RPF, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Further correction to already nomed mess., 2002 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Paris CoCo Report June, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Paris CoCo Ablage, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Harvard Coco Ablage, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - CC Budapest, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - RPF Materials --> LA meeting + beyond, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Intercultural Studies Project, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Intercultural Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - FILLM Archives inside ICLA Archives, 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - ICLA Archvies (Lausanne), 1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Ed. Consultant to CL, the comp., etc., 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Volume Theory & Practice of CL, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - AILC-ICLA XV August 1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Personal Pretoria Congress, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Travel Arrangements August 2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Table rounde - théorie Pretoria, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Pretoria, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - XVIth Congress South Africa, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - XVIth Congress of the International Comparitive LIterature Association, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Pretoria Agenda Items, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Treasury, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - List of participants, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Congress 2000 - Proposals (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - XVIth Congress China, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - XVIth Congress: Italy - Executive Council, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 16th Congress (General), 1997 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Info & Communication, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Secreatariat, 1994-1997 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Com. New Initiatives, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Lyric Traditions + Ruptures 94ff, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Research Com. Report, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Transition (Lambert), undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Comités de Tri, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Theory Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Finance 94ff, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Cultural + Literary Identity 94ff, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Committee on Info/Totosy 1999ff (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Voyage in Literature 94ff, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Issues + Methods 94ff, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Translation Committee, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Paris, Volume II, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Larsen Visit, 3-4 April, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Athens Bureau (6-7 November), 1998 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Travel Documents + Personalia, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - "Modernity" Res. Com., 1998 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Pretoria Congress 2000, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - South African Visit (Ablage), 1994 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Tahiiti Bureau, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - CC Tahiti, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Cultural Identity Committee (current), 1997 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Cultural Identity, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - GLL, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Reports of Adm., Com., + Editors (Leiden), 1998 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Announcements EC+GA Leiden + Agenda, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - EC meetings News of National Association, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Sondrup Bulletin, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - China Committee '88 ff, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - German 104 History of Literature, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Edinburgh A.A. Parker, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - LR/RL, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Review of CL Progress, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Deanery, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Humanities Circle, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - German Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - W. Lohnes Case, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - German Studies Selection, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Caldwell, 1981-1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Dean/University, 0 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - German Studies Flow Charts, Graduate Students, 1980-1983 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - German Studies Graduate Program Ablage, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - German Studies - Structure + Organization, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Graduate Advising, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Stanford German Studies Programs, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Lecturer Search, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Future of Leadership, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - German Studies Rosters, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - German Studies, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Decanal/University, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - German Studies, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 23)